{
    "id": "ead451074fe54a32b62656a651598a79",
    "title": "Past tense and past participle: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2805d30df70d4633b62d093eee39c8fd",
            "title": "Past And Past Participle Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He has …………………….. his own companion for the journey.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "select",
                        "selected",
                        "selecting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He would have ……………………… his speech after the break but the chairperson didn’t permit him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "resume",
                        "resumed",
                        "resuming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Has the problem ……………………….. solved?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "be",
                        "being",
                        "been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The accused ………………………. the jury’s verdict with anxiety.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "await",
                        "awaiting",
                        "awaited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "My watch was ……………………. by a boy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stole",
                        "stolen",
                        "stealed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A widespread outbreak of plague ……………………… in",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "occur",
                        "occured",
                        "occurred"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The song was …………………….. by Alice and her sister.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sang",
                        "sanged",
                        "sung"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The whole of the milk has been …………………….. by the cat.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "drank",
                        "drunk",
                        "drunked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was properly ………………………… with by the authorities.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "dealed",
                        "dealt"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………. the church regularly in my youth.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "attended",
                        "attending"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has ……………………… to China, so you can’t meet him now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "went",
                        "gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}